What up my good people? It is Sugar aka
Skinder Baby. So you see this fishing
behind. Anyways guys, I know that by the
title of this video, you guys already
know what's happening, right?
>> In 400 m at the roundabout
road.
>> And right now I went to buy a few things
that I need. I've been wanting this and
at the back there I had to buy the bag.
And yeah, guys, I'm I'll be vlogging my
whole day today and tomorrow cuz it's
going to take me two days to get to
Bloom. And I'll be checking out at half
3. I'll be arriving in Bloom. Actually,
I'll be arriving in Bloom around
12 midnight. Hope you guys enjoy the
video. Please don't forget to like,
share, comment, and subscribe and click
the notification button so you guys can
get notified every time SK Reezy drops
another video. Anyways, guys, stay
tuned.
Hello.
>> Anyways guys, I'm done getting ready and
now I'm on my way to I'm on my way to
the bus station which is Bman
and yeah, I got to get ready to go.
[music]
[laughter]
>> Anyways guys, next check is
>> [screaming]
>> Do you do you want to vent about it?
>> I guess.
So right now I've already packed
everything that belongs to SK. I
actually just packed myself to the boss
one. Then from there we're going home.
We are going home.
Yes.
I'm firstly going I'm first going to
meet up with my family. Then from there
we're going to meet up with my friends.
Then from there
>> then from there guys this lunch and the
vlog later on the vlog. I'll be vlogging
like I mentioned. I'll be vlogging for 2
days. two consecutive days because I'm
not going to arrive at blue today. I'm
arrive tomorrow early in the morning
around
1:00 a.m. Get myself. The drive is about
8 hours long. Am I going to be able to
sit that long?
Yes. Am I going to survive? No. Am I
going to come out that bus alive?
Probably. But anyway, guys, stay tuned.
Ah. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
[laughter]
Bring my bag,
man. Bring my bag.
Stop hitting the door. It's very
innocent. Bring my bag. Thank you. Yeah.
Yeah.
Obviously
Monday.
Now you're fighting.
>> Okay guys, so it's about time, right?
>> Yeah, peeps. It's about time now.
Mama.
>> Hi girls.
>> Yeah. Management
>> intro please.
Start your day. Let's go to the car and
call me short.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. B
>> like right now.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Mom checking in a day.
>> Yeah. She's taking me out.
>> When are you going to see Sunday?
>> Sunday.
I love you.
>> I
know. I wanted you to sign.
>> I should.
>> Oh, you can't. You want me to? What? I
wanted you just to sign your signature.
Ah [\h__\h]
>> [screaming]
>> Thank you.
[screaming]
[cheering]
>> You
>> [crying]
>> crazy.
Like there's no sign of it at all. But
then guys, here are my people.
>> Hi guys.
[screaming]
Anyways
guys, I might be delaying a bit. Right
now I'm on my way to Boston. I think I'm
a bit late. I'm quite sure. But we see
how we handle things.
Anyways
guys, so
um right now I'm waiting for my bus. Not
quite sure what time it's going to
arrive.
I just
Yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Bro, what's wrong with you?
She's here.
>> Hi, ma'am.
>> Hello, my baby.
>> Hey, guys. I've landed in blue. Um, to
be honest, that was the longest road
I've ever had since actually since I've
after I've went to Ptoria for the first
time. But now I'm here. I'll be vlogging
the whole night of today and tomorrow.
Yeah, guys. Just enjoy the rest of the
video.
>> Oh my gosh, guys. I missed my mom so so
much.
>> Hi Pinky. Hello my brother.
>> How are you Punky?
>> I'm good. I'm good.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my goodness. I feel like I'm freaking
out. [clears throat]
[laughter]
latest cat.
To be honest, the air here in PT is
different from the air in Ptoria. I mean
the air. Okay.
The air the air here in Boom is
definitely different from PCA
girl.
What's up YouTube?
Y guys, [screaming] I'm so excited to be
here. Like,
[laughter]
[snorts]
>> oh my gosh, guys. When did I see this
house?
>> No.
>> [laughter]
>> She's home,
[laughter]
guys.
>> I'm not done.
>> So, guys, [music]
[music] I'm a baby. [singing]
[music]
>> See you number one.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I got faith in you.
And now guys, you also see these people.
>> Yeah.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Let's go, GUYS.
[music]
OH, that was my the I'm holding it.
>> Yeah,
my bubble key. Hi guys.
I feel so short, bro.
>> Bro, what's wrong with you?
[music]
[singing]
I want this. Oh, guys. And it's only
[music]
2.2. Oh,
tinted.
[music]
So,
[music and singing]
[groaning and screaming]
this tree is fire. lady over there.
>> Ah, come on.
[music]
>> [music]